# **YAKIMA TENG**

Location: Shanghai

Email: veryplans@gmail.com

Phone: 184-5801-9856

Blog: http://www.orzzone.com/

## **PROFILE**

Job objective: frontend web development, Shanghai, 20K+, and friendly colleagues ^\_^

A man from Zhejiang, born in 1991. Self-motivated. Efficient in work. Enjoy writing (have a blog longer than 8 years), reading (130 books till now) and playing badminton (rewards).

#### **SKILL**

Familiar with common JS libraries/frames: <u>VueJS</u> \*\*\*\*\* > ReactNative+Redux \*\*\* > AngularJS \*\*.

Skilled in writing CSS3 (responsive design, LESS, flex, animation) \*\*\*\* (demo);

Had experience in developing a simple backend server with NodeJS (express) and MySQL (demo);

Comfortable with ES6, webpack/gulp, ESLINT, flow, git, jQuery, command line tools.

### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

Frontend Web Developer @ 天利有限公司上海分公司 | Dec 2015 - Present

- Frontend web development especially for SPA (i.e. single page application) in WeChat and Android/iOS APPs, and for traditional webpages in PC clients;
- Had independent developing experience in VueJS 1/2 for more than half a year;
- Participated in a long-term project outsourced by China Pacific Insurance using ReactNative+Redux;
- Maintained a Angular1 project.

Regulatory Affairs Person @ Zhejiang Apeloa Kangyu Pharmaceutical Co., Ltd. | Oct 2013 – Jul 2015

 Participated in audits by FDA and WHO. Provide submission for pharmaceuticals registration to foreign regulatory authorities, e.g. WHO, MOH of Ukraine, Taiwan Food and Drug Administrations.

#### **EDUCATION EXPERIENCE**

2009 - 2013: Graduated from Shenyang Pharmaceutical University with a B.S. degree in Pharmacy.

Before 2013: Skipped to junior middle school, recommended for admission to senior high school.